Preliminary Inventory of the Lee Edwards Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
Lee Edwards papers
1878-2004
2010C14
Hoover Institution Archives
340 manuscript boxes, 7 card file boxes, 4 oversize boxes, 5 film reels (146.4 linear feet)
Correspondence, speeches and writings, memoranda, reports, studies, financial records, printed matter, and sound recordings of interviews and other audiovisual material, relating to conservatism in the United States, the mass media, Grove City College, the Heritage Foundation, the Republican Party, Walter Judd, Barry Goldwater, and Ronald Reagan. Includes extensive research material used in books and other writing projects by Lee Edwards. Also includes papers of Willard Edwards, journalist and father of Lee Edwards.
Edwards, Lee
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2010.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Related Materials
Walter H. Judd papers, Hoover Institution Archives
Ronald Reagan subject collection, Hoover Institution Archives
Biographical Note
Edwards, a historian of American conservatism, has been the author or editor of over 20 books, including biographies of Ronald Reagan, Barry Goldwater, and Edwin Meese III, as well as histories of the Heritage Foundation and the conservative movement as a whole.
Edwards earned a doctorate in world politics from the Catholic University of America as well as a Bachelor of Arts degree in English from Duke University. He completed graduate work at The Sorbonne, Paris and received an honorary doctoral degree in humane letters from Grove City College.
An adjunct professor of politics at the Catholic University of America, Edwards was also the founding director of the Institute of Political Journalism at Georgetown University and a fellow at the Institute of Politics at the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University. Edwards was also a media fellow at the Hoover Institution.
A frequently guest on cable and broadcast outlets such as Fox News, CNN, Bloomberg, NBC, PBS, C-SPAN and NPR, Edwards has also been published in the Wall Street Journal, Los Angeles Times, Boston Globe, National Review, Human Events and American Spectator.
Among his awards and honors are the Millennium Star of Lithuania, the Cross of Terra Mariana of Estonia, the Friendship Medal of Diplomacy from the Republic of China (Taiwan), the John Ashbrook Award, the Reed Irvine Accuracy in Media Award and the Walter Judd Freedom Award.
Sources: Lee Edwards Staff Page: http://www.heritage.org/About/Staff/E/Lee-Edwards
Scope and Content of Collection
The collection contains a wide variety of materials documenting the life and work of Lee Edwards. Extensive research material used in books and other writing projects is included, relating to conservatism in the United States, the mass media, Grove City College, the Heritage Foundation, the Republican Party, Walter Judd, Barry Goldwater, and Ronald Reagan.
The collection also includes materials about the consulting firm Lee Edwards Associates, as well as documentation on Edwards' involvement in the Center for International Relations and Intercollegiate Studies Institute. In addition, personal papers of Lee Edwards, materials on his wife, Anne Edwards, and papers of Willard Edwards, journalist and father of Lee Edwards, are included. The papers include a variety of physical forms including correspondence, speeches, writings, memoranda, reports, studies, financial records, printed matter, sound recordings of interviews and other audiovisual material.
Edwards, Willard, 1902-1990.; Goldwater, Barry M. (Barry Morris), 1909-1998.; Grove City College.; Heritage Foundation (Washington, D.C.); Judd, Walter Henry, 1898-1994.; Reagan, Ronald.; Republican Party (U.S.: 1854- ); Conservatism--United States.; Mass media--United States.; Phonotapes.; United States--Politics and government--1945-1989.; United States--Politics and government--1989-; Video tapes.
- Lee Edwards personal papers
  Scope and Contents note
  Includes materials such as school exams, journals, memoirs, client files, articles, publications, and other miscellaneous materials. See also Writings and Research materials.
  - Early writings, school exams (Box 306-307)
  - Personal papers (Box 52-54, 55-57, 65-67, 74-76, 84, 209-212, 249-251,, 253, 299-300, 303)
  - Financial records (Box 131)
  - 1964 journal (Box 253)
  - Personal records and correspondence (Box 294-296)
  - Publications and books (Box 280, 302)
- Lee Edwards Associates records
  Contains materials documenting the work of Lee Edwards Associates political consulting firm.
  - General files (Box 90-93, 110-112, 185-187, 260-263)
  - ACWF (Box 154-157)
  - Life - PAC (Box 146)
  - Defalcation (Box 314-316)
- Anne Edwards papers
  Contains materials on or about Anne Edwards, wife of Lee Edwards.
  - General (Box 84)
  - Memoirs (Box 139-140)
- Willard Edwards papers
  Includes materials about journalist Willard Edwards, father of Lee Edwards
  - General (Box 1-2, 52-54, 84, 106-107, 158-160, 201-203)
  - Clippings (Box 77-82)
- Writings and research materials.
  Includes various research materials, manuscripts, files, and materials related to books published by Lee Edwards.
  - The Essential Ronald Reagan: a Profile in Courage, Justice, and Wisdom, published 2007
    - Research materials (Box 47-49, 99-100, 254)
    - 1970s and 1980s (Box 29-31, 32-33)
    - 1976 (Box 244-245)
    - Clippings, general (Box 118-122, 171-173, 204-206, 207-208)
    - Clippings, 1970s-1990s (Box 198-200)
    - Clippings, 1990s (Box 164-166)
    - Funeral, 2004 (Box 26-28)
  - The Conservative Revolution: the Movement That Remade America, published 2002
    - Conservative movement, late 1990s (Box 45-46, 127-128)
    - GOP 1980s. Includes Gingrich (Box 94-98)
    - Conservative movement history
    - G-P (Box 103-105)
    - P-Z (Box 42-44)
    - General (Box 232-233)
    - Conservative movement congressional files, early 1970s (Box 275-277)
    - Clippings (Box 238-239)
    - New right research materials (Box 252)
  - Mediapolitik: How the Mass Media Have Transformed World Politics, published 2001
    - Manuscript (Box 15-16)
    - Research materials (Box 188-190, 143-145, 147-151, 225-227, 242-243, 255-257, 268-269, 278-279, 281-282, 288-290,)
    - Miscellaneous politics (Box 87-89)
    - Media clippings (Box 270-271)
  - Freedom's College: The History of Grove City College, published 2000
    - Research materials (Box 3-6, 24-25, 36-38, 161-162, 222-224, 272-274, 304-305)
  - The Power of Ideas: The Heritage Foundation at 25 Years, published 1997
    - Research materials (Box 50-51)
    - Files, programs and publications (Box 22-23, 132-135)
    - Speaker files by name (Box 191-193)
  - Goldwater: The Man Who Made a Revolution, published 1995
    - Files, clippings, papers and research materials (Box 85-86, 101-102, 108-109, 113-117, 125-126, 129-130, 141-142, 177-178, 194-197, 264-267, 317-320, 321-322)
    - Congressional Record (Box 123-124)
    - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) (Box 228-229)
  - Missionary for Freedom the Life and Times of Walter Judd, published 1990
    - Files (Box 58-61, 72-83, 83,)
    - Books and reports (Box 258-259)
- Center for International Relations files
  Materials relating to Lee Edwards' work with the Center for International Relations.
  - General files (Box 34-35, 62-64,, 68-71, 84, 118-122, 297-298, 308-309)
  - Conference files (Box 136-138)
  - Board minutes (Box 179-181)
- Intercollegiate Studies Institute materials.
  Consists of documentation of the Intercollegiate Studies Institute
  - General (Box 12-14, 17-19, 39-41, 169-170, 174-176, 182-184, 234-237, 246-248)
- Printed matter and Miscellany
  - Serials (Box 163)
  - Media books (Box 310-313)
  - Miscellany (Box 20-21, 118-122)
- Oversize materials
  - Oversize items (Box 326-329)
- Framed photographs (Box 301)
- Video recordings (Box 7, 291-293)
- Sound recordings (Box 1, 8-11, 152-153, 163, 213-221, 330)
  - Lee Edwards interviews Ariel Cohen on 22 Apr 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Access
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005923
  - Lee Edwards interviews Barbara Wells and Sandy Sholte on 3 Dec 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006092
    This interview concerns Barry Goldwater.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Bill Simon and Jim Piereson, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005915
  - Lee Edwards interviews Bob Hubridy on 23 May 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005951
    This interview concerns the Heritage Foundation.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Bryan Johnsen on 5 Sep 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006090
    This interview concerns the Heritage Foundation and the conservative movement of the 20th century.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Burt Pines on 9 May 1996, 2 sound cassettes (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005943
  - Lee Edwards interviews Byron Lamm on 26 Apr 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005926
  - Lee Edwards interviews Charles Lichenstein on 4 Sep 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2000c120_a_0006085
  - Lee Edwards interviews Ed Hudgens on 28 May 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006071
  - Lee Edwards interviews Edwin J. Feulner on 11 Jun 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006078
  - Lee Edwards interviews Edwin J. Feulner on 6 Jun 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006076
  - Lee Edwards interviews Frank Shakespeare on 12 Apr 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005919
  - Lee Edwards interviews Hugh Newton on 14 May 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005949
    This interview concerns public relations and the conservative movement of the 20th century.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Jim Phillips on 17 Apr 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005921
  - Lee Edwards interviews Joe Bast on 25 Apr 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005925
  - Lee Edwards interviews John Goodman on 25 Apr 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005924
    Poor audio quality
  - Lee Edwards interviews John Gregory on 19 Apr 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005922
  - Lee Edwards interviews John O'Sullivan on 1 May 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005928
  - Lee Edwards interviews Karen Miller on 5 May 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005929
  - Lee Edwards interviews Kate O'Beirne on 3 Apr 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005918
  - Lee Edwards interviews Lloyd Laporte on 19 Sep 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006091
  - Lee Edwards interviews Margaret Bonilla on 29 Mar 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005916
  - Lee Edwards interviews Marvin Olasky on 25 Jul 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006079
    Via telephone.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Matthew Spalding on 24 May 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005955
  - Lee Edwards interviews Paul Weyrich on 17 Apr 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005920
  - Lee Edwards interviews Peter Pover on 8 May 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005930
    This interview concerns the Heritage Foundation and the conservative movement.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Phil Truluck on 26 Jul 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006083
  - Lee Edwards interviews Philip Crane on 25 Jul 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006081
  - Lee Edwards interviews Richard Allen on 7 Jun 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006077
  - Lee Edwards interviews Robert Blatz on 30 Jul 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006084
  - Lee Edwards interviews Robert Kreible on 23 May 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005953
  - Lee Edwards interviews Robert Rector on 23 May 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005954
  - Lee Edwards interviews Tom Moore on 21 May 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005950
  - Lee Edwards interviews Victoria Hughes on 29 May 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006072
  - Lee Edwards interviews Will Marshall on 10 May 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005946
  - Lee Edwards interviews William Beach on 14 May 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 10)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005947
  - Interviews with Rhett de Hart, Beth Personsi, and Joe Locoste, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006093
    These interviews, likely conducted by Edwards' daughter, concern the Heritage Foundation and the conservative movement.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Andy Little on 25 Apr 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006103
    This interview concerns the Buckeye Institute, the Heritage Foundation, and the conservative movement as a whole.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Baker Spring on 17 Apr 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006098
  - Lee Edwards interviews Bill Poole on 22 Apr 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006102
  - Lee Edwards interviews Bruce Weinrod on 4 Jun 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006469
  - Lee Edwards interviews Charles Murray on 27 Jun 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006484
    Conducted while Edwards was writing his book on the Heritage Foundation, this interview concerns Murray's work and the conservative movement of the 20th century.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Dan McMichael on 18 Nov 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006516
    This interview concerns the Heritage Foundation, think tanks, the conservative movement, and socialism in America.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Dan Mitchell on 17 Apr 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006101
  - Lee Edwards interviews David Abshire on 15 Jul 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006493
  - Lee Edwards interviews Dinesh D'Souza on 26 Jul 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006494
    This interview concerns D'Souza's experience with the Heritage Foundation.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Ed Feulner on 13 Jun 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006473
  - Lee Edwards interviews Ed Feulner on 26 Jun 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006479
    This interview concerns the turning points of the Heritage Foundation.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Ed Feulner on 5 Jun 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006470
  - Lee Edwards interviews Edwin Meese III on 30 Jul 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006499
  - Lee Edwards interviews Eugueni Volk on 3 Dec 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006524
  - Lee Edwards interviews Grace-Marie Arnett on 12 Sep 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006506
    Towards the beginning of the interview, Arnett goes out of her way to relate a story to Edwards. It concerns Carter in the 1980 election saying the Republicans are supposed to be the party that raises taxes out of fiscal responsibility and that the Democrats were supposed to be the party that knows how to spend that money. She says article she wrote about it went unpublished by her paper, but might be in the Carter library.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Irving Kristol on 18 Jun 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006474
    This interview concerns think tanks, focusing on Heritage and AEI, and neoconservativism.
    At the end, the conversation briefly touches on Newt Gingrich, repudiating the New Deal, and Robert Taft.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Jeane Kirkpatrick on 29 May 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006107
  - Lee Edwards interviews Jeff Eisenach on 3 Jun 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006110
  - Lee Edwards interviews Jeff Gayner on 3 Dec 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006520
  - Lee Edwards interviews John Dressendorfer on 19 Jun 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006475
    This interview concerns Ed Feulner
  - Lee Edwards interviews Ken Shaffer on 23 Sep 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006511
    This interview concerns the Heritage Foundation's work in Asia.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Linda Feulner on 6 Jun 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006472
    This interview concerns Mrs. Feulner's husband, Ed Feulner, and how his character relates to the Heritage Foundation.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Marshall Wittmann on 15 Apr 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006094
  - Lee Edwards interviews Marshall Wittmann on 18 Nov 1997, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006530
    This interview concerns Newt Gingrich. Wittmann is speaking largely off-the-record. Thus, while he is obviously respectful of and thinks highly of Gingrich, he details the shortcomings of Gingrich. He implies that being the leader of the majority changed Gingrich from the person that spent years learning in and leading the minority. He argues that Gingrich is trying to reshape the Republican Party in the way Franklin Roosevelt reshaped the Democratic Party. He then hypothesizes on what it will take to make Republican Party a long-term majority party.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Michael Armacest on 21 Jun 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006476
  - Lee Edwards interviews Mike Frank on 1 Jul 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006485
  - Lee Edwards interviews Milt Copulos on 3 Jun 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006108
  - Lee Edwards interviews Paul Weyrich on 5 May 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006104
  - Lee Edwards interviews Richard Fesher on 31 Jul 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006500
  - Lee Edwards interviews Robert Moffitt on 28 Feb 1997, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006525
    This interview concerns Moffitt's work at the Heritage Foundation and healthcare reform. Moffitt concentrates on his work pointing out the hypocrisy of liberals saying the public cannot making informed choices about healthcare plans when government workers make those choices every year.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Ron Wit on 27 Jun 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006480
  - Lee Edwards interviews Steve Winchell and Judy on 5 Jun 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006471
    This interview concerns the Heritage Foundation's use of direct mail.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Terry Scanlen on 5 Aug 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006501
  - Panel discussion on the 104th Congress from 23 Oct 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 11)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006512
    The Heritage Foundation convened this panel to discuss the actions of the 104th Congress and conservative ideas, not necessarily about the President or partisan controls.
  - An Audio View: Echoes of the American Republic, 1 sound cassette (Box 152)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005338
    This sound recording contains commentary on the international and domestic events of early 1991. Topics include the roots of Patriot Missile in SDI, the economies of Eastern Europe, the banking industry, SAT scores, understanding Oliver North and the Iran-Contra affair, acid rain, conservatives, the liberal view of Ronald Reagan, the judicial system in China, military equipment in Europe, and British WWII songs.
  - Barry Goldwater dictation sound recording answering the questions of Lee Edwards, 1.0 sound open reel tape (Box 152)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005344
    The program sounds like it was recorded sometime between the 1964 and 1966 elections.
  - Church music, 1 sound cassette (Box 152)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005345
    Cell. Recital 7/23/78
    Excerpts from "Sunday Excursion" + "Panis Angelicus"
    Church Solos: 1) O Holy Night
  - Lee Edwards interviews Ronald Reagan on 13 and 14 Oct 1965, 1.0 sound open reel tape (Box 152)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005382
    Edwards interviews Reagan just before Reagan's campaign for Governor of California.
  - Lee Edwards interviews W. Clement Stone on 29 Mar 1981, 1 sound cassette (Box 152)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0004851
  - National Right to Work Committee advertisements, 1.0 sound open reel tape (Box 152)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005347
    This ad criticizes Senator Howard Baker regarding the Helms amendment.
  - National Right to Work Committee advertisements, 1.0 sound open reel tape (Box 152)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005350
    The ads criticize Senate Majority Leader Howard Baker's efforts to block a vote on the Helms amendment regarding labor union practices.
  - National Right to Work Committee advertisements, 1.0 sound open reel tape (Box 152)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005351
  - National Right to Work Committee advertisements, 1.0 sound open reel tape (Box 152)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005352
  - Republican National Committee Mexican audio spots, 1.0 sound open reel tape (Box 152)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005342
    Topics: Impuestos (income tax), Inflacion (inflation), and Bush
  - Republican Party Hershey meeting on 12 Aug 1964 sound recording, 1.0 sound open reel tape (Box 152)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005372
    Featured speakers are Senator Barry Goldwater, Representative Bill Miller, President Dwight D. Eisenhower, Vice President Richard Nixon, Dean Burch.
    Many of the speeches are incomplete on the recording.